Guide to the Duke University Living History Program records, 1973-2005 and undated UA.22.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Living History Program records
1973-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Jay Rutherfurd Living History Program
UA.22.02.0001
41 Linear Feet
The Living History Program produces interviews with prominent American and world leaders who have been major participants in significant international or domestic events, or movements of social change. This collection contains videotapes and transcripts of interviews by Duke University faculty members with prominent American leaders, primarily in the area of post-World War II diplomacy.
Historical note
The Living History Program produces interviews with prominent American and world leaders who have been major participants in significant international or domestic events, or movements of social change. The Program is administered by the DeWitt Wallace Center for Media and Democracy in the Sanford School of Public Policy at Duke University.
Collection Overview
This collection contains videotapes and transcripts of interviews by Duke University faculty members with prominent American leaders, primarily in the area of post-World War II diplomacy. Individuals represented include Oscar Arias Sanchez, Les Aspin, Ellsworth Bunker, Dr. Samuel DuBois Cook, Angier Biddle Duke, J. William Fulbright, Averell Harriman, Jesse Jackson, Samuel W. Lewis, William H. Luers, Jack F. Matlock, George Crews McGhee, Robert McNamara, King Mihai of Romania, Yasuhiro Nakasone, Paula H. Nitze, Charles Percy, Dean Rusk, Abdus Salam, Terry Sanford, James Schlesinger, Earl E.T. Smith, Soedjatmoko, Hanna Suchaka, Richard Goldstone, Erhard Busek, Judy Woodruff, David Gergen, Vernon A. Walters, and Yegor Gaidar. Also includes a composite tape from the interviews with Bunker, Fulbright, and Rusk relating to perspectives on the war in Vietnam. The collection also includes videotapes of speeches given on the Duke campus by other prominent individuals.
Provenance
The Duke University Living History Program records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as multiple transfers starting in 1986.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Vietnam War, 1961-1965 -- United States; United States -- Foreign relations -- 1945-1989; Videocassettes; Cuban Missile Crisis, 1962; Transcripts; Poland; Austria; South Africa; Soviet Union; Jay Rutherfurd Living History Program
- Interviews, 1973-2005 and undated; 1
  - Arias, Oscar, 1991 April 12; 1
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 April 12 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0001)
      Scope and Contents note
      4-12-91; Arias Living History ISO Reel 1; 1 + 3 - Arias; 2 + 4 Panel
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 April 12 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0002)
      Living History Arias; Tape 1; 4-12-91; Program; 1 + 3 Arias; 2 + 4 Panel; 59:34
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 April 12 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0003)
      Living History Arias; 4/12/91; Program; Tape 2; 1 + 3 Arias; 2 + 4 Panel; 38:30
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 April 12 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0004)
      Living History; Arias; 4/12/91/ Tape 2; ISO; 1 + 3 Arias; 2 + 4 Panel
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 April 12 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0078)
      Duke University Living History Program presents A Conversation with Oscar Arias; Former President of Costa Rica; April 12, 1991; Part one - 59:34; Part Two - 38:30
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 April 12 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0079)
    - Transcript (5 copies), undated; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Aspin, Les, 1995 March 28; 2
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1995 March 28 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0005)
      Duke Living History; Les Aspen 2; 3/28/95; 34:46 with titles; master
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1995 March 28 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0006)
      Duke Living History; Les Aspen 1; 3/28/95; 54:54 with titles; master
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1995 March 28 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0076)
      Duke University Living History Program presents A Conversation with Les Aspin; Former United States Sectretary of Defense; March 28, 1995; Part one - 54:54; Part Two - 34:46
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1995 March 28 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0077)
    - Transcript (2 copies), undated (Box 25)
  - Axworthy, Lloyd, 2001 January 23; 3
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 2001 January 23 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0062)
      Duke Living History; Jan. 23, 2001; TRT 1:20:38; Lloyd Axworthy; Canadian Foreign Minister (1996-2000); Duke Recording Studios
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 2001 January 23 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0109)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents; A Conversation with Lloyd Axworthy; Former Canadian Minister of Foreign Affairs; recorded on January 23, 2001
  - Bond, Julian, 1988 April 5; 4
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 April 5 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0001)
      Julian Bond; 4/5/88; Tape 1
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 April 5 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0002)
      Julian Bond; 4/5/88; Tape 2
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, undated (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0091)
      Julian Bond Dub; view copy
  - Bork, Robert, 1988; 5
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 April 11 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0003)
      Robert Bork; 4-11-88; page Auditorium
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1988 May 9 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0082)
      Bork Dub 5-9-88; view copy
  - Bunker, Ellsworth, 1979 and undated; 6
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 26 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0004)
      Living History Series made possible by Jay Rutherford; Six Interviews with Ellsworth Bunker; (first of six); "General Background" with David Barber; Taped February 26, 1979, Duke University; work tape with time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 26 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0005)
      Living History Series made possible by Jay Rutherford; Six Interviews with Ellsworth Bunker; (second of six); "Vietnam" with Bruce Kuniholm; Taped February 26, 1979, Duke University; work tape with time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 26 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0006)
      Living History Series made possible by Jay Rutherford; Six Interviews with Ellsworth Bunker; (third of six); "India" with Ralph Braibanti; Taped February 26, 1979, Duke University; with time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 27 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0007)
      Living History Series made possible by Jay Rutherford; Six Interviews with Ellsworth Bunker; (fourth of six); "Latin America" with Arturo Valenzuela; Taped February 27, 1979, Duke University; with time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 28 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0008)
      Living History Series made possible by Jay Rutherford; Six Interviews with Ellsworth Bunker; (fifth of six); "Lecture Followup" with Taylor Cole; Taped February 28, 1979, Duke University; work tape with time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 28 (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0009)
      Living History Series made possible by Jay Rutherford; Six Interviews with Ellsworth Bunker; (sixth of six); "Europe" with Charles Maier; Taped February 28, 1979, Duke University; work tape with time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0010)
      Bunker-Barber 1; Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 2, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0011)
      Bunker-Barber 2; Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0012)
      Bunker-Barber 3; Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0013)
      Bunker - Barber cut-away reverses; Bunker - Kuniholm cut-aways reverses; tape 4; Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0014)
      Bunker - Kunihom cut-aways (cont); Bunker-Braibanti cut-aways; tape 4B; Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0015)
      Tape 4C; Press Conference; Bunker - Valenzuela cut-aways; Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0016)
      Tape 4D; Bunker - Valenzuela cut-aways (cont.); Bunker - Cole cutaways
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0017)
      Tape 4E; Cut-aways Bunker - Maier; Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0018)
      Barber-Kuniholm; Tape 1 (5); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0019)
      Barber-Kuniholm; Tape 2 (6); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0020)
      Barber-Kuniholm; Tape 3 (7); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0021)
      Barber- Braibanti; Tape 1 (8); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0022)
      Bunker-Braibanti; Tape 2 (9); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0023)
      Bunker-Braibanti; Tape 3 (10); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0024)
      Bunker-Valenzuela; Tape 1 (11); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0025)
      Bunker-Valenzuela; Tape 2 (12); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0026)
      Bunker-Valenzuela; Tape 3 (13); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0027)
      Bunker Speech; Tape 1 (14); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0028)
      Bunker Speech; Tape 2 (15); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 3, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0029)
      Bunker Speech; Tape 3 (16); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0030)
      Bunker - Cole; Tape 1 (17); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0031)
      Bunker - Cole; Tape 2 (18); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0032)
      Bunker - Cole; Tape 3 (19); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0033)
      Bunker - Maier; Tape 1 (20); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0034)
      Bunker - Maier; Tape 2 (21); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0035)
      Bunker - Maier; Tape 3 (22); Master Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 26 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0142)
      Living History Series; Ellsworth Bunker; #1 2/26/79; "General Background"
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 26 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0143)
      Duke University, Living History Program; Interview with Amb. Ellsworth Bunker; professor Barber, 26 Feb. 1979, 1 of 6; this is a dub of the master raw, unedited tape
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 26 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0144)
      Living History Series; Ellsworth Bunker; #2 2/26/79; "Vietnam"
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 26 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0145)
      Living History Series; Ellsworth Bunker; #3; "India"
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 27 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0146)
      Living History Series; 2/27/79; #4; An Interview with Ellsworth Bunker; "Latin American" with Arturo Valenzuela
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 Febuary 28 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0147)
      Living History Series; Ellsworth Bunker; "Europe"; 2/28/79
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 Febuary 28 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0148)
      Living History Series; 2/28/79; Ellsworth Bunker; "Lecture Followup"
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1979 February 27 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0149)
      Living History Series; Ellsworth Bunker; the Lecture "Diplomacy"; 2/27/79
    - Original audiocassette Audio-cassette, 1979 February 27 (Box 23, Audio-cassette UA.22.02.0001-CS-0001)
      Side A: Ellsworth Bunker, 000-705; start 017- Question and Answer and audience participation
    - Original audiocassette Audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette UA.22.02.0001-CS-0002)
      Duke Living History; 000-096 Intro: 1 side; Side 2: Press Conference
    - Original audiocassette Audio-cassette, 1979 February 28 (Box 23, Audio-cassette UA.22.02.0001-CS-0003)
      Duke Living History; Amb. Bunker; 2-28-79; Taylor Cole - 000-283; Prof Taylor Cole; Amb. Bunker; Wrap-up interview; 000-595; Feb. 28, 1979 - Italy 010; Making of Ambassador
    - Transcript (3 copies), 1979; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Transcript, clippings, 1979 (Box 25)
  - Busek, Erhard, 1997 April 10; 7
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1997 April 10 (Box 21, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0050)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with Erhard Busek; Former vice Premier of Austria; April 10 19972; Part One-1:22:10 Part Two-58:15; Part One
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1997 April 10 (Box 21, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0051)
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1997 April 10 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0053)
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1997 April 10 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0054)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with Erhard Busek; Former vice Premier of Austria; April 10 19972; Part One-1:22:10 Part Two-58:15; Part Two
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1997 April 10 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0055)
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1997 April 10 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0056)
    - Transcript (4 copies), 1998; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Clay, Lucius, undated; 8
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0140)
      General Clay Interview; Duplicate; Time 60:00
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0036)
      Jay Rutherfurd Collection; General Lucius Clay; CV5-504A; TBC Corrected
  - Composite, 1974 January; 9
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1974 January (Box 18, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0141)
      1) Introduction by Rugerfurd of audiovisual program; 2) Exceprts from interview with J.B. Rhine; 3) Interview with Sen. J. Sherman Cooper of Ky. After his retirement; Duke University; Rutherford collection; 22 minutes
  - Content Unkown, 1989 March 24; 10
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 March 24 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0119)
      ISO Cam 2; Tape 1; 3-24-89; Note attached reads: ISOs from Living History tapes that pre-date Scott Wells' tenure at Tech. Services. Content unknown
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 March 24 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0120)
      ISO Cam 2; Tape 2; 3-24-89; Note attached reads: ISOs from Living History tapes that pre-date Scott Wells' tenure at Tech. Services. Content unknown
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0121)
      Wide ISO; Tape #1; Note attached reads: ISOs from Living History tapes that pre-date Scott Wells' tenure at Tech. Services. Content unknown
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0122)
      Wide ISO; Tape #2; Note attached reads: ISOs from Living History tapes that pre-date Scott Wells' tenure at Tech. Services. Content unknown
  - Cook, Dr. Samuel DuBois, 1998 February 20; 11
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1998 February 20 (Box 21, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0048)
      Living History; Dr. Cook; Tape 1; 2/20/98; 58:30; Tape 1; Master
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1998 February 20 (Box 21, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0049)
      Living History; Dr. Cook; Tape 2; TRT 33:10; Master
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1998 February 20 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0057)
      Duke University Living History Program presents; An interview with Dr. Samuel DuBois Cook; President Emeritus, Dillard University; Professor Emeritus, Duke University; February 20, 1998; Part one - 58:30; Part Two-33:10
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1998 February 20 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0058)
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1998 February 20 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0059)
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, undated (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0105)
      Dr. Samuel DuBois Cook; Part 1: 58:30; Part 2: 33:10; Duke U Living History; Use copy
    - Transcript (2 copies), 1998 (Box 25)
  - Cooper, John Sherman, 1973 and undated; 12
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0037)
      Interview: John Sherman Cooper; Dick Rosse and Angier B. Duke; Master Copy?
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1973 November (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0038)
      Interview: John sherman Cooper Georgetown - Nov 1973; Edited Copy
  - Cristiani, Alfredo, 1998 May 18; 13
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1998 May 18 (Box 21, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0056)
      Living History; 5/18/98; tape 1; audio notes; Guest = tracks 1 + 3; Panel = tracks 2 + 4
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1998 May 18 (Box 21, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0057)
      Living History; 5/18/98; tape 2; audio notes; Guest = tracks 1 + 3; Panel = tracks 2 + 4
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1998 May 18 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0051)
      Duke University Living History Program presents; An interview with Alfredo Cristiani; President of El Salvador, 1989-1994; May 18, 1998; Part one - 57:11; Part Two-54:13
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1998 May 18 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0052)
  - Cuban Missile Crisis, excerpts from McNamara, Nitze, and Rusk, undated; 14
    - Transcript, undated (Box 25)
  - Davis, Walter, 1991 April 5; 15
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 April 5 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0007)
      4/5/91; Davis Living History; Tape 1; Program; 1 + 3 Davis; 2 + 4 panel; 57:14
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 April 5 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0008)
      50:00 of program (with credits); 4/5/91; Davis Living History; Tape 2 Program; 1 + 3 Davis; 2 + 4 Panel
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 April 5 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0009)
      4/5/91; Davis Living History; Tape 1; ISO; 1 + 3 Davis; 2 + 4 panel
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 April 5 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0010)
      4/5/91; Davis Living History; Tape 2; ISO; 1 + 3 Davis; 2 + 4 Panel
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 April 5 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0080)
      Duke University Living History Program presents A Conversation with Walter Davis; Duke University Trustee; April 5, 1991; Part one - 57:14; Part Two - 51:00
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 April 5 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0081)
      Duke University Living History Program presents A Conversation with Walter Davis; Duke University Trustee; April 5, 1991; Part one - 57:14; Part Two - 51:00; Use Copy
    - Transcript (2 copies), undated (Box 25)
  - Dole, Robert, 1988 March 1 and undated; 16
    - Original Video-cassette, undated (Box 19, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0156)
      Bob Dole; Viewing Copy
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 March 1 (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0039)
      Bob Dole Whistle Stop at duke; 3/1/88; Feed ch 1; Cam ch 2; Tape 1
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 March 1 (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0040)
      Bob Dole Whistle Stop at duke; 3/1/88; Feed ch 1; Cam ch 2; Tape 2
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 March 1 (Box 4, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0041)
      Bob Dole Whistle Stop at duke; 3/1/88; Feed ch 1; Cam ch 2; Tape 3
  - Duke, Angier Biddle, 1990 October 24; 17
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 October (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0123)
      European Journal, Oct. 1981; Interview with Angier Biddle duke, Senator George Pillsbury, and George E? Agree, members of the American Political Foundation re th estate of relations between the U.S. and othre members of the Western Alliance, particularly West Germany.
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1990 October 24 (Box 1, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0011)
      10-24-90; Living History; AB Duke with Robin; Program Reel 1; 1 - panel - +3; 2 - AB Duke - +3; 3-Panel - unity; 4 - AB Duke - Unity; Dub of Original; master
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1990 October 24 (Box 6, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0012)
      10-24-90; Living History; AB Duke w/ Robin; Program Reel 2; 1-panel-+3; 2-AB Duke-+3; 3-Panel-Unity; 4-AB Duke-Unity; Dub of Original; Master
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1990 October 24 (Box 6, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0013)
      10-24-90; Living History; AB Duke with Robin; program Reel 3; Dub of original; end reel 3 reel 4; Master
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1990 October 24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0001)
      Living History; 10-24-90; AB Duke w/ Robin; Program Reel 1; Master
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1990 October 24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0002)
      Living History; 10-24-90; AB Duke w/ Robin; Program Reel 2
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1990 October 24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0003)
      Living History; 10-24-90; AB Duke w/ Robin; Program Reel 3
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1990 October 24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0004)
      Living History; 10-24-90; AB Duke w/ Robin; Program Reel 4
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1990 October 24 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0092)
      Duke University Living History Program presents A Conversation Angier Biddle Duke; former United States Ambassador; also Robin Duke; October 24, 1990; Tape one: 1:31:13